<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Blog &#8211; New Jobs in Dubai</title>
	<atom:link href="/blog/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:19:02 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.6.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2024/09/cropped-icons8-jobs-64-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Blog &#8211; New Jobs in Dubai</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">143460714</site>	<item>
		<title>Flydubai Careers &#8211; Airline Jobs in Dubai</title>
		<link>/flydubai-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:18:59 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Elevate your career in the airline industry with Flydubai Careers in Dubai. Flydubai offers excellent job opportunities for individuals eager to pursue their professional aspirations. With less stringent requirements and a family-like atmosphere, Flydubai provides an ideal platform to turn your career goals into reality. Join Flydubai today, embark on a journey with them, and ... <a title="Flydubai Careers &#8211; Airline Jobs in Dubai" class="read-more" href="/flydubai-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Flydubai Careers &#8211; Airline Jobs in Dubai">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Flydubai Careers - Airline Jobs in Dubai",
  "hiringOrganization": "Flydubai Careers",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 35702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "Flydubai offers a diverse range of job opportunities across various departments, catering to individuals with different skills and expertise. As of the latest information, here are some types of jobs available at Flydubai in the UAE.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Elevate your career in the airline industry with Flydubai Careers in Dubai. Flydubai offers excellent job opportunities for individuals eager to pursue their professional aspirations. With less stringent requirements and a family-like atmosphere, Flydubai provides an ideal platform to turn your career goals into reality. Join Flydubai today, embark on a journey with them, and soar to new heights in your career.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Flydubai</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">United Arab Emirates</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Jobs:</strong></h2>



<p>Flydubai offers a diverse range of job opportunities across various departments, catering to individuals with different skills and expertise. As of the latest information, here are some types of jobs available at Flydubai in the UAE:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Cabin Crew:</strong> Responsible for ensuring the safety and comfort of passengers during flights.</li>



<li><strong>Pilot:</strong> Flying and operating aircraft, ensuring the safety of the flight and passengers.</li>



<li><strong>Ground Staff:</strong> Roles in areas such as check-in, boarding, baggage handling, and customer service at airports.</li>



<li><strong>Call Center Customer Service:</strong> Handling customer inquiries, providing information, and addressing issues.</li>



<li><strong>Engineering Positions:</strong> Including roles such as Aircraft Maintenance Engineer, Avionics Engineer, and Mechanical Engineer.</li>



<li><strong>Technical Operations:</strong> Involving tasks related to aircraft maintenance, repairs, and technical support.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>About Flydubai:</strong></h2>



<p>Flydubai is a low-cost airline based in Dubai, UAE, founded in 2008 and operational since 2009. With a fleet of over 60 Boeing 737 planes, FlyDubai serves more than 95 destinations across the Middle East, Asia, Africa, and Europe. The airline focuses on providing affordable air travel, punctuality, and safety. Offering passengers customization options for entertainment, meals, and baggage, FlyDubai has received numerous awards for its customer-centric service.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Cabin Crew Jobs at Flydubai:</strong></h2>



<p>Flydubai is committed to providing opportunities for individuals at all experience levels. From innovative trainees to participants in the Internship Program, the airline offers training and special benefits. Experienced professionals can explore roles such as Cabin Crew, Call Center Customer Service, Pilot, and Ground Staff. Flydubai emphasizes inclusivity and encourages individuals to be open to the possibilities for a rewarding career.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits and Salary in Flydubai UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Flydubai offers a range of competitive salary packages and benefits, including health insurance, performance-based bonuses, travel benefits, training opportunities, a positive work environment, employee recognition programs, discounts, and career advancement prospects. The airline is dedicated to supporting work-life balance.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How To Apply for a Job at Flydubai UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>To apply for Flydubai Careers in Dubai, follow these steps:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>Visit the official Flydubai website and navigate to the &#8220;Careers&#8221; section.</li>



<li>Explore available job openings and choose the one that aligns with your qualifications.</li>



<li>View the detailed job description, requirements, and responsibilities.</li>



<li>Prepare an updated resume highlighting your skills, experience, and education.</li>



<li>Create an account or sign in to the Flydubai careers portal to submit your application online.</li>



<li>Upload your resume and any additional requested documents.</li>



<li>Verify the accuracy of all information before submitting the application.</li>



<li>Monitor your email and the Flydubai careers website for application status updates.</li>
</ol>



<p>By following these steps, efficiently apply for Flydubai Careers in Dubai and enhance your chances of joining this renowned airline.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Flydubai UAE</td><td><a href="https://careers.flydubai.com/search-and-apply/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Flydubai Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">442</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>DHA Careers &#8211; Dubai Health Authority Jobs</title>
		<link>/dha-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:18:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=445</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The Dubai Health Authority (DHA), established in 2007, oversees and supervises the healthcare industry in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. Committed to providing top-notch healthcare services to Dubai citizens, DHA manages a network of hospitals, clinics, and healthcare facilities across the emirate. With a focus on enhancing public health and wellness, DHA also trains healthcare professionals, ... <a title="DHA Careers &#8211; Dubai Health Authority Jobs" class="read-more" href="/dha-careers/" aria-label="Read more about DHA Careers &#8211; Dubai Health Authority Jobs">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "DHA Careers - Dubai Health Authority Jobs",
  "hiringOrganization": "DHA Careers",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 48702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "Dubai Health Authority regularly updates its job openings, offering various opportunities for medical staff and support personnel. Recent job opportunities at DHA span nursing, management, finance, IT, and clinical specialties such as emergency medicine, radiology, and cardiology. DHA emphasizes equal opportunities for all, promoting inclusion and diversity in its workforce. Interested candidates can view and apply for the latest job postings on our website or through online employment portals.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>The Dubai Health Authority (DHA), established in 2007, oversees and supervises the healthcare industry in Dubai, United Arab Emirates. Committed to providing top-notch healthcare services to Dubai citizens, DHA manages a network of hospitals, clinics, and healthcare facilities across the emirate. With a focus on enhancing public health and wellness, DHA also trains healthcare professionals, implements healthcare policies, and conducts health education programs. As a crucial entity, DHA ensures that all residents in Dubai have access to high-quality healthcare at reasonable costs.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Dubai Health Authority (DHA)</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dubai" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Dubai</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Working Culture at Dubai Health Authority:</strong></h2>



<p>Working at the Dubai Health Authority (DHA) comes with numerous advantages, including competitive pay and benefits, opportunities for professional growth, and a welcoming work environment. DHA fosters a culture of innovation and quality while valuing diversity. As a government entity, DHA provides stability and job security. Employees at DHA have the unique opportunity to contribute to the community&#8217;s health and well-being while joining a passionate team of healthcare professionals dedicated to delivering high-quality care.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities at Dubai Health Authority:</strong></h2>



<p>Dubai Health Authority (DHA) regularly updates its job openings, offering various opportunities for medical staff and support personnel. Recent job opportunities at DHA span nursing, management, finance, IT, and clinical specialties such as emergency medicine, radiology, and cardiology. DHA emphasizes equal opportunities for all, promoting inclusion and diversity in its workforce. Interested candidates can view and apply for the latest job postings on the DHA website or through online employment portals.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Nursing Jobs at DHA Dubai Health Authority:</strong></h2>



<p>DHA provides a range of nursing positions across different disciplines, including emergency, pediatrics, and critical care. Acknowledging the crucial role of nurses in delivering high-quality patient care, DHA offers opportunities for career progression, educational growth, and a positive work environment.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Pharmacist Jobs at Dubai Health Authority:</strong></h2>



<p>DHA offers diverse positions for pharmacists in hospital pharmacies, neighborhood pharmacies, and specialty clinics. Recognizing the significance of pharmacists in aiding patients with medication management, DHA pharmacists collaborate with medical specialists to ensure safe and effective medication use.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits of Working with Dubai Health Authority:</strong></h2>



<p>Joining Dubai Health Authority offers several benefits, including:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Advancement in professional standing within a center for cutting-edge medical innovation.</li>



<li>Extensive opportunities for ongoing learning and professional growth.</li>



<li>Prioritization of employee wellbeing and work-life balance.</li>



<li>Collaboration with a supportive team of professionals to stimulate growth and discoveries.</li>



<li>Competitive pay and benefits while contributing to Dubai&#8217;s world-class medical system.</li>



<li>Engagement in innovative programs and facilities shaping the future of healthcare.</li>



<li>A reputable organization dedicated to promoting career and personal development.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How To Apply for a Job at Dubai Health Authority:</strong></h2>



<p>To apply for DHA Careers in the healthcare industry:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>Visit the official DHA website and browse current job listings.</li>



<li>Choose a position aligned with your skills and experience.</li>



<li>Click &#8220;Apply Now&#8221; to access DHA&#8217;s e-recruitment platform.</li>



<li>Register or log in, provide personal details, and submit your CV.</li>



<li>Fill out the online application form, ensuring accuracy.</li>



<li>Monitor your email for communications from DHA regarding application status.</li>
</ol>



<p>Embark on a rewarding career in the healthcare industry with DHA Careers and contribute to the well-being of the community.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Dubai Health Authority UAE</td><td><a href="https://jobs.dubaicareers.ae/careersection/dubaicareers/jobsearch.ftl?ignoreSavedQuery&amp;f=ORGANIZATION(36105011891)&amp;lang=en" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">DHA Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">445</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Medcare Hospital Careers: Jobs in UAE</title>
		<link>/medcare-hospital-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:18:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=846</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Medcare Hospital offers diverse prospects for individuals enthusiastic about making a positive impact on patient care. The institution cultivates a supportive environment for professional growth, emphasizing patient-centered care and a commitment to achieving high standards of excellence. Whether you&#8217;re an experienced healthcare professional or a recent graduate, Medcare Hospital provides a platform to showcase your ... <a title="Medcare Hospital Careers: Jobs in UAE" class="read-more" href="/medcare-hospital-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Medcare Hospital Careers: Jobs in UAE">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Medcare Hospital Careers: Jobs in UAE",
  "hiringOrganization": "Medcare Hospital",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 58702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "Medcare Hospital in the UAE offers a variety of job opportunities across different departments to cater to the diverse needs of its healthcare services. Here are some types of jobs you might find at Medcare Hospital UAE.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Medcare Hospital offers diverse prospects for individuals enthusiastic about making a positive impact on patient care. The institution cultivates a supportive environment for professional growth, emphasizing patient-centered care and a commitment to achieving high standards of excellence. Whether you&#8217;re an experienced healthcare professional or a recent graduate, Medcare Hospital provides a platform to showcase your skills and expertise. Join their esteemed team and become part of a compassionate workforce dedicated to delivering exceptional healthcare services.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Medcare Hospital</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">United Arab Emirates</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities:</strong></h2>



<p>Medcare Hospital in the UAE offers a variety of job opportunities across different departments to cater to the diverse needs of its healthcare services. Here are some types of jobs you might find at Medcare Hospital UAE:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Physicians and Surgeons:</strong> Medical professionals providing specialized care in various fields, including internal medicine, surgery, pediatrics, gynecology, etc.</li>



<li><strong>Nurses:</strong> Registered nurses, nurse practitioners, and other nursing staff responsible for patient care, monitoring, and coordination.</li>



<li><strong>Pharmacists:</strong> Professionals managing medication dispensing, advising patients on drug usage, and ensuring adherence to safety protocols.</li>



<li><strong>Technicians and Technologists:</strong> Individuals specializing in medical imaging, laboratory testing, and other diagnostic procedures.</li>



<li><strong>Administrative Staff:</strong> Roles in administration, including receptionists, administrative assistants, HR specialists, and finance professionals.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>About Medcare Hospital:</strong></h2>



<p>Medcare Hospital stands as a leading healthcare institution, renowned for its unwavering commitment to delivering exceptional medical services. Striving for excellence in patient outcomes, the hospital employs advanced technologies and follows evidence-based practices. The patient-centric approach ensures individualized attention and personalized treatment plans. Embracing a multidisciplinary approach, Medcare integrates expertise with compassionate care, consistently enhancing benchmarks to provide top-notch healthcare services and achieve favorable health results.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits &amp; Salary:</strong></h2>



<p>Medcare Women’s and Children’s Hospital Careers offer a range of benefits, including:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Competitive Compensation</li>



<li>Exciting Incentives</li>



<li>Robust Healthcare</li>



<li>Performance-Based Bonuses</li>



<li>Work-Life Balance Support</li>



<li>Professional Growth</li>



<li>Attractive Salary</li>



<li>Lucrative Benefits Included</li>



<li>Comprehensive Rewards</li>



<li>Generous Remuneration</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Apply for a Job at Medcare Hospital UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Applying for Medcare Hospital Careers in the UAE is a straightforward process. Visit the official Medcare website, navigate to the Careers section by clicking the “Apply Here” button, and explore the list of available job opportunities. Identify positions aligned with your skills and aspirations, prepare a well-crafted resume, and submit your application through the online portal, ensuring to complete all required fields and attach necessary documents. This streamlined process offers you the chance to embark on a fulfilling healthcare career with a reputable institution dedicated to excellence.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Medcare Hospital UAE</td><td><a href="https://hcdt.fa.us2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX/requisitions?location=United+Arab+Emirates&amp;locationId=300000000254942&amp;locationLevel=country&amp;mode=location" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Medcare Hospital Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">846</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>ADAC Careers &#8211; New Vacancies in Abu Dhabi UAE</title>
		<link>/adac-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:18:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Abu Dhabi Airports Company (ADAC) stands at the forefront of the aviation industry, managing and operating airports, including the prestigious Abu Dhabi International Airport. Committed to excellence and innovation, ADAC focuses on delivering exceptional services and experiences. With a well-trained workforce, the company ensures top-notch passenger handling, cargo operations, aircraft maintenance, and air traffic management. ... <a title="ADAC Careers &#8211; New Vacancies in Abu Dhabi UAE" class="read-more" href="/adac-careers/" aria-label="Read more about ADAC Careers &#8211; New Vacancies in Abu Dhabi UAE">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "ADAC Careers - New Vacancies in Abu Dhabi UAE",
  "hiringOrganization": "Abu Dhabi Airports Company",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 48702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "ADAC offers competitive salaries and a range of attractive benefits, including lucrative salary packages, comprehensive employee benefits, generous perks, competitive pay scales, exciting incentives, excellent remuneration, and impressive employee rewards. Financially rewarding opportunities await those who join the ADAC team.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Abu Dhabi Airports Company (ADAC) stands at the forefront of the aviation industry, managing and operating airports, including the prestigious Abu Dhabi International Airport. Committed to excellence and innovation, ADAC focuses on delivering exceptional services and experiences. With a well-trained workforce, the company ensures top-notch passenger handling, cargo operations, aircraft maintenance, and air traffic management. Actively contributing to aviation sector growth through partnerships and sustainability initiatives, ADAC strategically invests in infrastructure, technology, and human capital to maintain its global leadership in the industry.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Abu Dhabi Airports Company (ADAC)</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Abu_Dhabi" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Abu Dhabi</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Job Openings:</strong></h2>



<p>As of the information, specific job titles or openings at Abu Dhabi Airports Company (ADAC) are not explicitly listed. However, the general categories of jobs that may be available at ADAC, as is commonly found in airport management organizations, include:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Airport Operations:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Ground Operations</li>



<li>Terminal Operations</li>



<li>Baggage Handling</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Aviation Management:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Aviation Security</li>



<li>Air Traffic Management</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Customer Service:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Passenger Services</li>



<li>Customer Relations</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Engineering and Maintenance:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Aircraft Maintenance</li>



<li>Facilities Maintenance</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Administration:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Human Resources</li>



<li>Finance</li>



<li>Administration</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Information Technology:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>IT Security</li>



<li>Systems Administration</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Working Culture at ADAC:</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Inclusive Environment:</strong> ADAC places a strong emphasis on diversity and equitable opportunities, encouraging individuals from various backgrounds to thrive in its workforce.</li>



<li><strong>Empowering Females:</strong> The company is dedicated to empowering females, fostering an environment of fairness and growth, making it an inclusive workplace for all.</li>



<li><strong>Comprehensive Training Programs:</strong> As a leading organization, ADAC is committed to nurturing talent through comprehensive training programs, ensuring continuous learning and skill development.</li>



<li><strong>Innovation Culture:</strong> ADAC fosters a culture of innovation, providing employees with the opportunity to contribute to groundbreaking developments in the aviation industry.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits:</strong></h2>



<p>ADAC offers competitive salaries and a range of attractive benefits, including lucrative salary packages, comprehensive employee benefits, generous perks, competitive pay scales, exciting incentives, excellent remuneration, and impressive employee rewards. Financially rewarding opportunities await those who join the ADAC team.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">How to Apply for a Job at ADAC UAE:</h2>



<p>To explore the latest job opportunities with ADAC, follow these steps:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li>Visit the official ADAC careers website at workforce.hirecraft.ae.</li>



<li>Click on the &#8220;Apply Now&#8221; button to browse available job opportunities.</li>



<li>Review job listings and click on the desired position to view detailed job descriptions and requirements.</li>



<li>Prepare an updated resume highlighting relevant skills and experiences.</li>



<li>Fill out the online application form with accurate and complete information.</li>



<li>Attach your resume and any other requested documents.</li>



<li>After submission, the ADAC recruitment team will review your application and contact you if shortlisted for further evaluation.</li>
</ol>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Abu Dhabi Airports Company UAE</td><td><a href="https://workforce.hirecraft.ae/careers/#/jobsearch" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ADAC Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">559</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Serco Careers &#8211; Jobs in Serco Middle East</title>
		<link>/serco-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:18:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=436</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Unlock an exceptional career opportunity by applying for Serco Careers – a gateway for both novices and seasoned professionals. Serco, situated in Dubai, offers an enticing prospect to secure a robust job, especially in the dynamic Dubai Metro. This could be your chance for professional growth; read on if you&#8217;re intrigued. Company Name Serco Job ... <a title="Serco Careers &#8211; Jobs in Serco Middle East" class="read-more" href="/serco-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Serco Careers &#8211; Jobs in Serco Middle East">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Serco Careers - Jobs in Serco Middle East",
  "hiringOrganization": "Serco Careers",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 48702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "Serco offers diverse job options, from customer service agents to operations managers, maintenance technicians, and project managers. The company provides the ideal environment for professionals seeking career advancement in a vibrant and creative setting, with a focus on diversity and inclusivity.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Unlock an exceptional career opportunity by applying for Serco Careers – a gateway for both novices and seasoned professionals. Serco, situated in Dubai, offers an enticing prospect to secure a robust job, especially in the dynamic Dubai Metro. This could be your chance for professional growth; read on if you&#8217;re intrigued.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Serco</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">United Arab Emirates</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Jobs:</strong></h2>



<p>Serco UAE offers a diverse range of job opportunities across various sectors, including defense, healthcare, and transportation. As of the latest information, here are some types of jobs available at Serco UAE:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Customer Service Agents:</strong> Providing assistance and support to customers, ensuring a positive experience.</li>



<li><strong>Operations Managers:</strong> Overseeing and managing the day-to-day operations of various projects or services.</li>



<li><strong>Maintenance Technicians:</strong> Responsible for the maintenance and upkeep of equipment and facilities.</li>



<li><strong>Project Managers:</strong> Leading and managing specific projects, ensuring successful completion within deadlines.</li>



<li><strong>Finance and Accounting Positions:</strong> Including roles such as Accountant, Financial Analyst, and Finance Manager to handle financial aspects.</li>



<li><strong>Human Resources Specialists:</strong> Handling recruitment, employee relations, training, and other HR functions.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>About Serco:</strong></h2>



<p>Serco, a leading provider of public services in Dubai, specializes in defense, healthcare, and transportation. Operating in over 30 countries, Serco brings international expertise and a commitment to quality. In Dubai, Serco manages the technologically advanced Dubai Metro. The company is dedicated to enhancing people’s lives through top-notch services, seeking bright individuals to join their team and contribute to innovation and development in the UAE.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Working Culture at Serco:</strong></h2>



<p>Serco UAE fosters a vibrant workplace, emphasizing diversity, creativity, and collaboration. Employees dedicated to excellence are empowered to share their ideas, creating an inviting atmosphere. A keen sense of professionalism, support for skill development, and open communication contribute to a cohesive workplace. Serco values work-life balance, ensuring employee well-being and satisfaction.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits of Working at Serco:</strong></h2>



<p>Serco offers competitive compensation packages, and benefits such as gratuities, yearly leave, and health insurance. The organization promotes career growth, professional development, and a culture of rewards and recognition.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities at Serco UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Serco offers diverse job options, from customer service agents to operations managers, maintenance technicians, and project managers. The company provides the ideal environment for professionals seeking career advancement in a vibrant and creative setting, with a focus on diversity and inclusivity.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Apply for a Job at Serco UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Visit the official website, select “Careers,” and browse open positions. Choose a role, review prerequisites, and click “Apply Now” to submit your resume and required documentation. Track your application status online and follow up as needed.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Serco UAE</td><td><a href="https://careers.serco.com/ME/search/?createNewAlert=false&amp;q=&amp;locationsearch=AE" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Serco Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">436</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Commercial Bank of Dubai Careers &#8211; UAE Jobs</title>
		<link>/commercial-bank-of-dubai-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:17:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=571</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Commercial Bank of Dubai (CBD) stands as a prominent financial institution in the United Arab Emirates, renowned for its innovation and commitment to customer service. Established in 1969, CBD has evolved into a full-service commercial bank, offering a diverse range of products and services to individuals, businesses, and governmental organizations. Committed to fostering economic growth ... <a title="Commercial Bank of Dubai Careers &#8211; UAE Jobs" class="read-more" href="/commercial-bank-of-dubai-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Commercial Bank of Dubai Careers &#8211; UAE Jobs">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Commercial Bank of Dubai Careers - UAE Jobs",
  "hiringOrganization": "Commercial Bank of Dubai Careers",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 48702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "Commercial Bank of Dubai offers a variety of job opportunities, including roles in relationship management, credit analysis, marketing, compliance, software development, and cybersecurity. The bank actively encourages talented individuals from diverse backgrounds to apply, valuing the richness that diversity brings to the workplace.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Commercial Bank of Dubai (CBD) stands as a prominent financial institution in the United Arab Emirates, renowned for its innovation and commitment to customer service. Established in 1969, CBD has evolved into a full-service commercial bank, offering a diverse range of products and services to individuals, businesses, and governmental organizations. Committed to fostering economic growth in the UAE through ethical lending and investment practices, CBD has received numerous accolades for its superior banking practices. With a network of branches across the UAE, CBD is a trusted partner for clients seeking reliable financial solutions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Commercial Bank of Dubai (CBD)</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dubai" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Dubai</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Job Openings:</strong></h2>



<p>CBD typically offers a range of job opportunities across various departments and functions within the banking sector. Common job categories at a bank like CBD may include:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Relationship Management:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Relationship Manager</li>



<li>Relationship Officer</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Credit Analysis:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Credit Analyst</li>



<li>Credit Risk Manager</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Marketing:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Marketing Specialist</li>



<li>Marketing Executive</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Compliance:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Compliance Officer</li>



<li>Anti-Money Laundering (AML) Analyst</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Software Development:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Software Developer</li>



<li>IT Specialist</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Cybersecurity:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Cybersecurity Analyst</li>



<li>Information Security Officer</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits of Working at Commercial Bank of Dubai:</strong></h2>



<p>Embark on an exciting and fulfilling career at the Commercial Bank of Dubai, where opportunities for growth and advancement abound. CBD invests in the education and professional development of its staff, providing the tools needed for success. The bank fosters a supportive and collaborative work environment that encourages creativity, innovation, and the recognition of excellence. Joining CBD means working for a renowned company dedicated to making a positive impact on the UAE&#8217;s economy while enjoying competitive pay and benefit packages.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities at Commercial Bank of Dubai:</strong></h2>



<p>Commercial Bank of Dubai offers a variety of job opportunities, including roles in relationship management, credit analysis, marketing, compliance, software development, and cybersecurity. The bank actively encourages talented individuals from diverse backgrounds to apply, valuing the richness that diversity brings to the workplace.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Qualifications and Requirements:</strong></h2>



<p>Qualifications and requirements vary based on the specific roles; however, the following are general considerations:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>A university degree in a relevant discipline is typically required.</li>



<li>Prior work experience in the banking or financial services sector is preferred.</li>



<li>Strong interpersonal and communication skills.</li>



<li>Proficiency in both Arabic and English is often required.</li>



<li>Knowledge of national and international banking rules is advantageous.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Apply for Commercial Bank of Dubai:</strong></h2>



<p>If you aspire to join the CBD team, ensure that your profile aligns with the position requirements. Take the time to review the criteria and tailor your application accordingly. Submit a well-crafted application with a subject line that specifies the job opening. If not selected, view it as an opportunity for skill enhancement and future success. Seize the chance to contribute to the success of the Commercial Bank of Dubai by applying for exciting career opportunities.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Commercial Bank of Dubai UAE</td><td><a href="https://www.cbd.ae/careers/career-with-us/overview/apply" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Commercial Bank of Dubai Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">571</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Air Arabia Careers &#8211; Jobs in Sharjah UAE</title>
		<link>/air-arabia-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:16:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=556</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Air Arabia stands as the pioneering and largest low-cost carrier in the Middle East and North Africa (LCC). Since its establishment in 2003, Air Arabia has been steadfast in providing affordable air travel to millions of customers across the region. Operating from its primary hub at Sharjah International Airport, the airline connects nearly 170 destinations ... <a title="Air Arabia Careers &#8211; Jobs in Sharjah UAE" class="read-more" href="/air-arabia-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Air Arabia Careers &#8211; Jobs in Sharjah UAE">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Air Arabia Careers - Jobs in Sharjah UAE",
  "hiringOrganization": "Air Arabia Careers",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 48702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "As of the latest, Air Arabia offers a range of job openings in various departments. The types of job openings at Air Arabia may include positions in the following categories.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Air Arabia stands as the pioneering and largest low-cost carrier in the Middle East and North Africa (LCC). Since its establishment in 2003, Air Arabia has been steadfast in providing affordable air travel to millions of customers across the region. Operating from its primary hub at Sharjah International Airport, the airline connects nearly 170 destinations spanning the Middle East, Africa, Asia, and Europe. Committed to fostering employment opportunities, Air Arabia invites individuals passionate about aviation to join their team.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Air Arabia</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">United Arab Emirates</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Job Openings:</strong></h2>



<p>As of the latest, Air Arabia offers a range of job openings in various departments. The types of job openings at Air Arabia may include positions in the following categories:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Aircraft Crew:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>A320 Captain</li>



<li>A320 First Officer</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Cabin Crew:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Cabin Crew Members</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Ground Staff:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Customer Service Agent</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Technical Positions:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>IT Security Engineer</li>



<li>Aircraft Painter</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Working Culture at Air Arabia:</strong></h2>



<p>Air Arabia places a strong emphasis on the progress and prosperity of its staff, fostering a dynamic and diverse work environment that reflects its dedication to employees. The airline values collaboration and innovation, essential qualities in the aviation sector. Each team member is regarded as a valuable asset, with deep respect for their unique skills and qualities. With a strong commitment to employee well-being and career development, Air Arabia cultivates a nurturing and supportive atmosphere, enabling everyone to thrive. Through its focus on innovation, adherence to ethical principles, and an abundance of career prospects, Air Arabia exemplifies an ideal workplace. Joining Air Arabia means becoming part of a vibrant team that prioritizes quality.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Employee Benefits at Air Arabia:</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Air Arabia provides competitive salaries to its staff.</li>



<li>In addition to wages, employees enjoy benefits such as healthcare coverage and travel perks.</li>



<li>The airline offers professional development programs to support career advancement.</li>



<li>Flight crew personnel receive additional benefits, including accommodation, travel, and health insurance.</li>



<li>Employees and their families can avail of discounts on Air Arabia tickets.</li>



<li>Requirements to Work at Air Arabia</li>



<li>Qualifications vary based on the job position, typically including education, relevant experience, and English language proficiency.</li>



<li>For flight and cabin crew positions, criteria such as age, height, and physical fitness apply.</li>



<li>Technical roles require specific knowledge and credentials.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Apply for a Job at Air Arabia:</strong></h2>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>To apply for Air Arabia Careers in Dubai, follow these steps:</li>



<li>Visit the official Air Arabia website.</li>



<li>Navigate to the &#8220;Careers&#8221; section.</li>



<li>Browse job vacancies in Dubai.</li>



<li>Select a position and click &#8220;Apply Now.&#8221;</li>



<li>Create a new account or sign in.</li>



<li>Provide your name and contact information.</li>



<li>Upload your cover letter and latest CV.</li>



<li>Review and submit your application.</li>



<li>Keep an eye on your inbox for emails from Air Arabia.</li>
</ul>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Air Arabia UAE</td><td><a href="https://careers.airarabia.com/airarabia/search/?createNewAlert=false&amp;q=&amp;locationsearch=ae" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Air Arabia Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p>If selected, prepare for assessments and interviews. Best of luck with your application.</p>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">556</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mastercard Careers: Jobs in Dubai UAE</title>
		<link>/mastercard-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=849</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A career with MasterCard goes beyond earning a living; it is a chance to establish a lifelong partnership with an organization that values your dedication and hard work. Discover the current job opportunities and explore the list of MasterCard&#8217;s newest job postings to find roles perfectly suited to your career aspirations. Company Name Mastercard Job ... <a title="Mastercard Careers: Jobs in Dubai UAE" class="read-more" href="/mastercard-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Mastercard Careers: Jobs in Dubai UAE">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Mastercard Careers: Jobs in Dubai UAE",
  "hiringOrganization": "Mastercard",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 59702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "MasterCard presents various roles across different locations and functions globally. Recent job openings cover fields such as IT, finance, marketing, product management, law, and more. Whether you're an experienced professional or starting your career, MasterCard provides opportunities to collaborate with highly skilled experts dedicated to fostering innovation and delivering excellent value to customers. Access to training and development programs enhances your skills and furthers your career, making you part of a cutting-edge business influencing the direction of digital payments.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>A career with MasterCard goes beyond earning a living; it is a chance to establish a lifelong partnership with an organization that values your dedication and hard work. Discover the current job opportunities and explore the list of MasterCard&#8217;s newest job postings to find roles perfectly suited to your career aspirations.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Mastercard</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">United Arab Emirates</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Jobs:</strong></h2>



<p>Mastercard, being a global payments and technology company, offers a variety of job opportunities in the UAE across different functions and departments. Here are some types of jobs you might find at Mastercard UAE:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Software Engineer:</strong> Responsible for developing and maintaining software applications and systems.</li>



<li><strong>Product Manager:</strong> Manages the development and launch of new products, ensuring alignment with business goals.</li>



<li><strong>Business Development Manager:</strong> Focuses on expanding Mastercard&#8217;s business by identifying and pursuing new opportunities.</li>



<li><strong>Financial Analyst:</strong> Analyzes financial data, prepares reports, and provides insights to support decision-making.</li>



<li><strong>Marketing Specialist:</strong> Plans and executes marketing campaigns, promotes products, and enhances brand visibility.</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>About MasterCard:</strong></h2>



<p>Operating in over 210 countries and territories, MasterCard is a leading provider of global payments and technology. Established in 1966, MasterCard offers a range of financial services, including digital payment options, credit, debit, and prepaid cards. The company&#8217;s mission is to connect individuals, organizations, and economies to foster progress and prosperity. Dedicated to advancing inclusivity and innovation in the financial sector, MasterCard continues to shape the future of digital payments worldwide, focusing on security, convenience, and reliability.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits &amp; Salary:</strong></h2>



<p>Joining MasterCard means becoming part of a vibrant, forward-thinking organization committed to making a global impact. As an employee, you&#8217;ll collaborate with diverse individuals, access training and development opportunities, and contribute to a culture of collaboration and innovation. MasterCard supports diversity and inclusion, offering various benefits to promote employee well-being, along with competitive salary packages. Being part of the MasterCard team means contributing to changing how people pay and conduct business worldwide.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities at MasterCard UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>MasterCard presents various roles across different locations and functions globally. Recent job openings cover fields such as IT, finance, marketing, product management, law, and more. Whether you&#8217;re an experienced professional or starting your career, MasterCard provides opportunities to collaborate with highly skilled experts dedicated to fostering innovation and delivering excellent value to customers. Access to training and development programs enhances your skills and furthers your career, making you part of a cutting-edge business influencing the direction of digital payments.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How To Apply for a Job at Mastercard UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Interested candidates can visit the official website, navigate to the &#8220;Careers&#8221; section, and explore available job opportunities. After selecting a suitable opening, fill out the online application form, attaching your resume and cover letter. Additional materials may be required for specific positions. Following the application, candidates may undergo further evaluation, such as a phone or video interview, to determine their suitability for the role. Join MasterCard and be part of a pioneering organization shaping the future of digital payments.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Mastercard UAE</td><td><a href="https://careers.mastercard.com/us/en/search-results?keywords=United%20Arab%20Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Mastercard Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">849</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fakeeh University Hospital Careers &#8211; Dubai UAE</title>
		<link>/fakeeh-university-hospital-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:16:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fakeeh University Hospital, located in Dubai, United Arab Emirates, is a modern healthcare facility offering a comprehensive range of services, including emergency care, surgery, cancer treatment, cardiology, neurology, pediatrics, and more. The hospital is dedicated to patient-centered care and employs the latest medical technology. With a team of highly skilled medical professionals, including doctors, nurses, ... <a title="Fakeeh University Hospital Careers &#8211; Dubai UAE" class="read-more" href="/fakeeh-university-hospital-careers/" aria-label="Read more about Fakeeh University Hospital Careers &#8211; Dubai UAE">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "Fakeeh University Hospital Careers - Dubai UAE",
  "hiringOrganization": "Fakeeh University Hospital",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 15702.00,
    "maxValue": 59702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "Fakeeh University Hospital frequently posts job vacancies for various positions, including medical, administrative, and support roles. The hospital seeks individuals passionate about the medical field, equipped with the necessary training and credentials, and committed to providing patients with compassionate and individualized care. Current openings include positions in nursing, radiography, pharmacy, laboratory, administration, and more. Working at Fakeeh University Hospital offers a unique opportunity to contribute to healthcare in Dubai with a focus on patient-centered care, innovation, and a supportive community.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Fakeeh University Hospital, located in Dubai, United Arab Emirates, is a modern healthcare facility offering a comprehensive range of services, including emergency care, surgery, cancer treatment, cardiology, neurology, pediatrics, and more. The hospital is dedicated to patient-centered care and employs the latest medical technology. With a team of highly skilled medical professionals, including doctors, nurses, and support workers, Fakeeh University Hospital provides compassionate and individualized care to each patient. The hospital is committed to advancing health and wellness through education and research collaborations with prestigious universities and a specialized research center.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Fakeeh University Hospital</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dubai" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Dubai</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Jobs:</strong></h2>



<p>Fakeeh University Hospital typically includes positions in various departments and roles. These may include:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Medical and Clinical Positions:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Physicians (Specialists and Consultants)</li>



<li>Nurses (Registered Nurses, Nurse Practitioners)</li>



<li>Allied Health Professionals (Pharmacists, Radiographers, Laboratory Technicians, etc.)</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Administrative and Support Positions:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Administration and Operations</li>



<li>Human Resources</li>



<li>Finance and Accounting</li>



<li>Information Technology</li>



<li>Customer Service</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Patient Care and Services:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Patient Care Coordinators</li>



<li>Medical Assistants</li>



<li>Patient Services Representatives</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Research and Development:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Research Scientists</li>



<li>Clinical Research Coordinators</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Technical and Engineering Roles:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Biomedical Engineers</li>



<li>Facilities Management</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits of Working at Fakeeh University Hospital Dubai:</strong></h2>



<p>Joining Fakeeh University Hospital provides the opportunity to work in a cutting-edge healthcare environment with access to the latest scientific research and technological advancements. The hospital fosters a friendly, collaborative work atmosphere that encourages professional growth. The culturally diverse community promotes a positive working environment for both patients and staff. With a focus on diversity and inclusivity, the hospital offers internal career growth opportunities, attractive compensation, and benefits.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities at Fakeeh University Hospital Dubai:</strong></h2>



<p>Fakeeh University Hospital frequently posts job vacancies for various positions, including medical, administrative, and support roles. The hospital seeks individuals passionate about the medical field, equipped with the necessary training and credentials, and committed to providing patients with compassionate and individualized care. Current openings include positions in nursing, radiography, pharmacy, laboratory, administration, and more. Working at Fakeeh University Hospital offers a unique opportunity to contribute to healthcare in Dubai with a focus on patient-centered care, innovation, and a supportive community.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Qualifications and Requirements:</strong></h2>



<p>Qualifications and requirements vary based on the specific roles; however, the following are general considerations:</p>



<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Suitable education and experience are typically required for different roles.</li>



<li>Passion for medicine and dedication to providing compassionate, individualized patient care.</li>



<li>Effective interpersonal, teamwork and problem-solving skills are highly valued.</li>



<li>Ability to work in a diverse workplace, demonstrating cultural sensitivity and awareness.</li>



<li>English fluency is a requirement, and proficiency in other languages may be preferred for certain professions.</li>



<li>Background checks and pre-employment screenings may be conducted.</li>
</ul>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Apply for a Job at Fakeeh University Hospital UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Candidates interested in Fakeeh University Hospital careers can visit the hospital&#8217;s official website and navigate to the &#8220;Careers&#8221; tab. There, they can explore available job postings and submit an online application, including a cover letter and resume. Applicants should ensure they meet the qualifications for the desired position and provide any required documents. Successful candidates may receive offers of employment after interviews or additional testing. Fakeeh University Hospital welcomes applications from qualified individuals driven to enhance healthcare in Dubai. Seize the opportunity to contribute to healthcare excellence by joining Fakeeh University Hospital.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Fakeeh University Hospital UAE</td><td><a href="https://careers.fuh.care/search/?createNewAlert=false&amp;q=&amp;locationsearch=&amp;optionsFacetsDD_dept=&amp;optionsFacetsDD_customfield1=" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Fakeeh University Hospital Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">568</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>P&#038;G Careers &#8211; Vacancies in Dubai UAE</title>
		<link>/pg-careers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[James]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2024 12:16:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Blog]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">//?p=565</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Procter &#38; Gamble (P&#38;G), a renowned global consumer products company headquartered in Cincinnati, Ohio, USA, has been shaping industries since 1837. With a commitment to creating household and personal care products under well-known brands like Pampers, Tide, Gillette, and Crest, P&#38;G operates in over 180 countries with a workforce of approximately 95,000 individuals. The company&#8217;s ... <a title="P&#38;G Careers &#8211; Vacancies in Dubai UAE" class="read-more" href="/pg-careers/" aria-label="Read more about P&#38;G Careers &#8211; Vacancies in Dubai UAE">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<!-- JSON-LD markup generated by Google Structured Data Markup Helper. -->
<script type="application/ld+json">
{
  "@context": "http://schema.org/",
  "@type": "JobPosting",
  "title": "P&G Careers - Vacancies in Dubai UAE",
  "hiringOrganization": "Procter & Gamble (P&G)",
  "jobLocation" : [
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "United Arab Emirates"
  },
 {
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Dubai, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates"
  },
{
    "@type" : "Place",
    "address" : "Sharjah, United Arab Emirates"
  }
],
  "datePosted": "2024-12-27",
  "baseSalary": {
    "@type": "MonetaryAmount",
    "currency": "AED",
    "value":{
    "@type": "QuantativeValue",
    "minValue": 16702.00,
    "maxValue": 59702.00,
    "unitText": "MONTH"}
  },
  "description": "P&G offers a broad spectrum of employment opportunities, spanning marketing, sales, engineering, research & development, and finance. Recent openings include roles such as brand manager, research scientist, supply chain manager, financial analyst, and client business development manager. These diverse roles cater to individuals with varied skill sets and specialties, available in different parts of the world. P&G actively promotes inclusion and diversity, making it an attractive workplace for individuals from all backgrounds.",
  "employmentType": "Full Time",
  "validThrough": "2025-06-30"
}
</script>



<p>Procter &amp; Gamble (P&amp;G), a renowned global consumer products company headquartered in Cincinnati, Ohio, USA, has been shaping industries since 1837. With a commitment to creating household and personal care products under well-known brands like Pampers, Tide, Gillette, and Crest, P&amp;G operates in over 180 countries with a workforce of approximately 95,000 individuals. The company&#8217;s mission is to enhance consumers&#8217; lives through innovative goods and services, all while championing social responsibility and sustainability. P&amp;G fosters a diverse and inclusive workplace, providing ample opportunities for professional growth.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td><strong>Company Name</strong></td><td>Procter &amp; Gamble (P&amp;G)</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Job Location</strong></td><td><a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_Arab_Emirates" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">United Arab Emirates</a></td></tr><tr><td><strong>Qualifications</strong></td><td>High school / Degree Diploma or Equivalent</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Application Type</strong></td><td>Online</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Recruitment Type</strong></td><td>Full Time</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Nationality</strong></td><td>Any</td></tr><tr><td><strong>Benefits</strong></td><td>As per UAE labor law</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Type of Job Openings:</strong></h2>



<p>The specific job openings at Procter &amp; Gamble (P&amp;G) can vary over time, and the available positions cover a wide range of functions and roles. However, P&amp;G typically offers opportunities in various areas, including but not limited to:</p>



<ol class="wp-block-list">
<li><strong>Marketing:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Brand Manager</li>



<li>Marketing Analyst</li>



<li>Digital Marketing Specialist</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Sales:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Sales Representative</li>



<li>Key Account Manager</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Research &amp; Development:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Research Scientist</li>



<li>R&amp;D Engineer</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Supply Chain:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Supply Chain Analyst</li>



<li>Logistics Manager</li>
</ul>
</li>



<li><strong>Finance:</strong>
<ul class="wp-block-list">
<li>Financial Analyst</li>



<li>Finance Manager</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ol>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Benefits of Working at P&amp;G UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Joining P&amp;G means becoming part of a multinational corporation dedicated to improving lives. The company cultivates a multicultural and inclusive work environment that recognizes each employee&#8217;s contributions and encourages both personal and professional development. P&amp;G employees take pride in their work and its societal impact, driven by the company&#8217;s focus on innovation and sustainability. P&amp;G strives to establish a work environment where individuals can thrive on both personal and professional fronts.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>Job Opportunities at P&amp;G UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>P&amp;G offers a broad spectrum of employment opportunities, spanning marketing, sales, engineering, research &amp; development, and finance. Recent openings include roles such as brand manager, research scientist, supply chain manager, financial analyst, and client business development manager. These diverse roles cater to individuals with varied skill sets and specialties, available in different parts of the world. P&amp;G actively promotes inclusion and diversity, making it an attractive workplace for individuals from all backgrounds.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading"><strong>How to Apply for a Job at P&amp;G UAE:</strong></h2>



<p>Candidates can explore job openings in Dubai on the official P&amp;G website and submit their applications. By creating a profile, adding a resume, and applying for desired positions, candidates can take the first step towards a rewarding career with P&amp;G. Additionally, attending career fairs or recruitment events hosted by P&amp;G provides valuable insights into the company and its employment opportunities. It&#8217;s advisable for applicants to thoroughly review job descriptions and requirements before applying to ensure alignment with the skills and background required for the position. Seize the opportunity and pursue a fulfilling career with P&amp;G in Dubai.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table class="has-base-2-background-color has-background"><tbody><tr><td>Apply at Procter &amp; Gamble UAE</td><td><a href="https://www.pgcareers.com/global/en/locations/united-arab-emirates#job-search" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">P&amp;G Careers</a></td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p><a href="/">Home</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">565</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
